What happened to David Palmer wasn't supposed to happen.
大卫・帕默的事本来不该发生的
He put himself in harm's way,
他让他自己身处险境
and he got involved with something that he shouldn't have.
他牵涉进了一些本不应牵涉进的事情
You know who killed David?
你知道是谁杀了大卫
He works for me.
那人是我的人
You lied to me.
你骗了我
This entire day has been one giant lie!
这一天就是一个巨大的谎言
What you've done makes me sick!
你的所作所为让我作呕
Martha, enough!
玛莎 够了
I need you to swear to me
你发誓
that you will do as I ask for the country.
发誓为了这个国家 你会按我说的做
I hate you.
我恨你
The situation with Martha is taken care of.
玛莎的问题已经解决了
There are too many loose ends lying around.
出了太多的岔子
We cannot afford to have her pull on one and unravel everything.
不能把她牵涉进来 要是她把事情都抖出来就糟了
She won't.
她不会的
I have the recording.
我拿到录音了
Have you destroyed it?
是否已经把它毁掉了
No, sir, I have not.
没有 总统先生
You and I have been in this from the beginning.
你我从一开始就牵涉在这事情里
Destroying that recording protects both of us.
把录音毁掉对我们俩都有好处
I've got O'brian.
找到奥布赖恩了
Where is she?
她在哪里
She's working  out of Bill Buchanan's house.
在比尔・布坎南家里
Did Chloe tell you why she was helping Audrey raines and Bauer?
科洛伊有没有跟你 说为什么要帮奥黛丽和鲍尔
'Cause she thinks Jack is innocent,
她说杰克是清白的
that President Logan framed Bauer.
说洛根总统陷害了鲍尔
This is Karen Hayes
我是凯伦・海因斯
Miles traced Chloe to your house.
迈尔斯追踪到科洛伊在你家
You have less than seven minutes to get Chloe out of there.
你要在七分钟内让科洛伊离开
Karen, why are you warning us?
凯伦 你为什么要帮我们
Because I may have made a mistake earlier.
因为我之前可能犯了个错误
Chloe,
科洛伊
if they find you here, you'll be arrested.
如果他们在这里找到你 会把你抓起来的
You have to go now.
你现在就得走
Not yet.
还没好
It's over, Christopher!
一切都结束了克里斯托夫
Turn around!
转过身来
Give me the recording.
把录音给我
I don't have it.
不在我这里
Where is it?!
在哪里
Henderson wasn't lying.
亨德森没说谎
He doesn't have the recording on him.
录音不在他身上
There must've been some kind of a hand-off.
一定是在半路上给了什么人
Henderson stopped and rendezvoused with another car.
亨德森停下来与另一辆车相会
Can you track the other car?
能追踪到那辆车吗
We're tracking it now, Jack.
正在追踪
It headed back to van nuys
车子开回了范内斯机场
looks like the civilian side of the airfield
好象是去了机场的民用区
pulled onto the tarmac;
开上了跑道
whoever it was got out and got directly onto the plane.
那人直接上了飞机
It is a chartered diplomatic flight.
是个特许的外交航班
Jack, we've tried everything we can.
杰克 我们已经试过了一切办法
There's no way to delay the plane.
没办法延迟飞机起飞
The following takes place between 2Am and 3Am.
以下是发生于凌晨2点至3点之间的故事
Okay, call me when you've got 'em.
好的 抓到后打电话给我
Bill, are you out?
比尔 你离开没
The field team's almost there.
外勤队快到了
Chloe's packing the comm gear she needs to stay in touch with Jack.
科洛伊正在收拾电脑设备 以便和杰克保持联系
Where is Jack?
杰克在哪里
Van nuys airport.
范内斯机场
He stowed away on a diplomatic flight that just took off.
他潜入了一架刚起飞的外交客机
What? Why?
什么 怎么回事
He's trying to find a recording that implicates President Logan.
他在找一份能够揭露洛根总统的录音
And someone on that flight has it?
录音在飞机上某个人手中
Yes, and we don't know who.
是的 但不知道是哪个人
That's what Chloe's been trying to find out.
科洛伊正在查到底是谁
Hang on.?
稍等
Field team's a block away from Buchanan's.
外勤队离布坎南的家还有一个街区
I'll set up here for the remote debrief of O'brian.
我要在这里对奥布赖恩的审讯进行监督
No. Put it in the situation room.
不 到会议室去吧
I thought you wanted...
我以为你要在
I want it in the situation room.
去会议室
Go.
去吧
Bill, the field team's gonna be there any second.
比尔 外勤组马上就到了
Get Chloe out of there now.
让科洛伊马上离开
How close are they?
他们还有多远
One block.
一个街区
All right, I'm gonna have to run interference.
好的 我得帮她挡一下
It's more important that she gets away.
她一定得跑掉
Good. I'll bring you in.
好的 假装把你抓回来
You'll be treated as a suspect.
你将被视作一名嫌犯
We never talked.
我们没有谈过话
Understood.
明白
They're here.
他们到了
Out the back.
从后门走
Bill, wait.
比尔 等一下
Have Chloe call me on a dry channel.
让科洛伊从D线给我打电话
Either one-five or two-seven.
15号或者27号
Dry channel,one-five or two-seven.
D线 15号或者27号
Got it.
收到
There's a gate in back.
后面有扇门
Follow the path between the houses to the alley,
从房子中间的小路往小巷里走
turn right and go to ventura boulevard.
然后右转上文托拉大街
What about the curfew?
外面在宵禁啊
There's a hotel on the boulevard,the miramont.
街边有个酒店 叫麦拉蒙特酒店
You should be able to make it there without being spotted.
进那家酒店不会被发现的
What about you?
那你怎么办
I'm gonna make sure you're not followed.
我要确保你不被跟踪
I'll be at CTU,probably in holding.
我会在CTU 很可能被拘禁
Why in holding?
为什么要拘禁你
Karen's gonna place me under arrest.
凯伦要拘捕我
If you need anything,
有任何需要的话
contact her.
跟她联系
-Why is she... -Chloe, please, just go.
-她为什么  -科洛伊 别说了 快走
Who is it?
谁啊
Homeland security.
国土安全部
Mr. Buchanan,we need you to open the door.
布坎南先生 请开门
We're under order from Karen Hayes.
我们奉凯伦・海因斯的命令
I'll be right there.
来了
What, what's going on?
怎么回事
Please step aside, sir.
请让开 长官
We need to search the house.
我们要搜查屋子
No, I'm not stepping aside.
不 我不让开
Do you have a warrant?
有搜查令吗
Where's Chloe O'brian?
科洛伊・奥布赖恩在哪里
I have no idea.
我不知道
Sir,
长官
don't make us use force
别逼我们来硬的
we know she's been here.
我们知道她在这里
Look, I don't know what you're talking about.
听着 我不知道你们在说什么
Where is she?
她在哪里
I don't know where Chloe O'brian is.
我不知道科洛伊・奥布赖恩在哪里
She's not here.
她不在
Sir?
长官
This is a recent file from comm.
这是网络上的最新的文件
Only O'brian could access it.
只有奥布赖恩能够进入获得这文件
Talk to us, sir.
说吧 长官
I'm not talking to you.
我不跟你们说
I'll talk to Karen Hayes.
我要跟凯伦・海因斯说
Papazian,
我是帕帕赞恩
Mr. Papazian,
帕帕赞恩先生
we are on site it appears Chloe O'brian was here,
我们到了 现场表明科洛伊・奥布赖恩曾经来过
but she is gone.
但现在跑了
Is Bill Buchanan there?
比尔・布坎南在吗
Yes, sir.
在 长官
We lost O'brian.
奥布赖恩跑了
Damn it!
糟糕
Put him on the phone, please.
请让他听电话
Hello?
喂
Don't play games with me, Bill.
别玩游戏了 比尔
Just give me O'brian's location,
告诉我奥布赖恩在哪里
or I will make it very bad for you.
否则你将会有大麻烦
From what I understand,
据我所知
Miles, she got out of CTU right under your nose.
迈尔斯 她从你的眼皮子底下跑出了CTU
You're the one who ought to be concerned, not me.
你才会有麻烦 而不是我
Bill, this is Karen Hayes.
比尔 我是凯伦・海因斯
Tell us what you know now.
现在就告诉我们你所知道的情况
Stop wasting our time.
别再浪费我们的时间
I'm not saying any more.
我没别的话说了
This is ed.
我是艾德
Ed, bring Buchanan in.
艾德 把布坎南带回来
Set up a grid search for Chloe.
设置网格搜索寻找科洛伊
She's probably got a car,
她很可能开车逃跑
which means she's about 15 Miles out.
也就是说可能已经在15英里以外了
Copy that.
收到
But the agents on site are trained for interrogation.
但是现场的探员接受过审讯训练
Why are you bringing him in?
为什么要把他带回来呢
Because I want to run this, Miles.
因为我要亲自审他 迈尔斯
But now it's us who are wasting time here.
现在是我们在浪费时间了
Don't worry.
别担心
I will make him talk.
我会让他招供的
I'll be in my office.
我回我办公室
I'm set up at the miramont hotel.
我在麦拉蒙特酒店
Make sure no one looks for me here.
确保没人到这里来抓我
I'll take care of that.
我会解决这问题的
Tell me what else you need.
你还有什么需要吗
Jack's on diplomatic flight 520.
杰克在520号外交航班上
Pull up the manifest.
把乘客名单找出来
Got it. Flight 520 to frankfurt.
找到了 520号航班飞往法兰克福
Okay, put everything you've got from that flight under the shared volume
好的 把关于那航班的所有信息 都存放到共享文档中
so I can get to it.
这样我能看到这些信息
Crew, passengers, cargo,everything.
机组成员 乘客 货物 所有信息
Done.
好了
Okay, I see it.
好的 看到了
Thanks.
谢谢
Jack, are you okay?
杰克 还好吧
I'm fine.Did you get what I need?
还好 找到我要的信息了吗
I've got the passenger list
找到了乘客名单
it's gonna take some time to cross it against Henderson.
搜索和亨德森相关的信息要一些时间
What about the air marshal?
空警的信息呢
That I'll have in a couple of minutes.
一两分钟就能搞定
Okay, good.
好的
What's happening at CTU?
CTU怎么样
They're still under orders from the President to stop you,
他们依然奉总统之命缉拿你
but Karen Hayes is backing us.
但是凯伦・海因斯在帮我们
Openly?
公开地
No, but she's letting me help you.
不 但她让我帮你
If there's proof against Logan,
如果有指证洛根的证据的话
she wants it found.
她希望找到那些证据
The proof is on this plane.
证据就在这架飞机上
Check the flight manifest,
查一下飞机的名单
figure out which passenger has a connection to Henderson
看看哪个乘客和亨德森有关联
and get back to me with the air marshal's seat number.
找出空警的座位号 然后打电话个我
I will.
好的
I don't think so.
我可不这样想
I was just asking.
我只是问问
You don't have to go all feminist on me.
你没必要跟我来女权主义那一套
Did you see that?
看到没
21st-century woman.
21世纪的女性
We better get used to it.
我们最好慢慢习惯
Jack, I found the air marshal
杰克 找到空警的信息了
his name is george avila.
他名叫乔治・阿维拉
He's sitting in 7a.
坐在7A座
Anyone sitting next to him?
他旁边有人坐吗
No.
没有
Okay, good.
好的
Get back to me when you've got the connection to Henderson.
找到和亨德森 有关联的人后打电话给我
Got it.
收到
Excuse me.
对不起
Is that seat taken?
这个座位有人吗
No.
没有
Thanks.
谢谢
The stewardess said I could change seats
服务员说可以换座位
I was next to the galley,
我的座位在厨房旁边
it's kind of noisy.
有点吵
I'm trying to get some rest.
我想休息一下
Okay, the man you're looking for is in seat 12d.
你要找的人在12D座位
His name is Hans Meyer.
他叫汉斯・梅尔
He's with the german government.
德国政府的人
He's been connected to omicron since the mid-1990s.
从90年代中期起和欧米克隆公司有联系
He's worked directly with Henderson.
他与亨德森有直接合作关系
That's it.
就这些了
Okay, I've got it.
知道了
Mr. Meyer?
梅尔先生?
Yes?
什么?
My name is george avila.
我是乔治・阿维拉
I'm the air marshal on this flight.
机上的空警
What's wrong?
什么事情?
It's nothing serious.
不是大问题
We found something that we think is yours.
我们找了你的东西
It should have been in the baggage compartment.
一定是在行李仓
We'd just like you to come back to the galley
我们想请你出来
and identify it for us
鉴别下
so we can properly stow it.
这样我们不会载错行李
Please, sir. We'd  really appreciate it.
请来吧 十分感谢
If you have any carry-on bags,
如果你随身带有行李
you should bring them with you.
也请一同带上
I don't.
我没有
Very well.
好的
What makes you think it was mine?
为什么认为是我的?
Ticket stub.
机票存根
They have taken away all my medication.
他们拿走了所有的药
I need to get to it.
而我现在要服用
I'm sorry, ma'am.
抱歉 夫人
They won't let me give that to you.
他们不允许我给您
What do they think I'm going to do?
他们怎么想的?
Kill myself?
我要自杀?
Over that son of a bitch?!
是那个杂种说的?
I just called the President of the United States a son of a bitch.
我刚说美国总统是个蠢狗日的
No reaction?
你怎么没反应?
He must have some kind of law on the books against that,
他一定不能忍受
or am I immune,
为什么不找我问罪
just like he is?
我像他那样有特权?
Do you have a first name,agent Adams?
你的名是什么 亚当斯特工?
It's Justin, ma'am.
贾斯丁 夫人
You don't have much of a personality, do you, Justin?
你是块呆木头 贾斯丁
This is Novick.
我是诺维克
It's Martha.
是玛莎
Are you still in the retreat?
你还在官邸吗?
Yes. I'm just down the hall from your room.
是的 就在你门前大厅的尽头
I need you to come here right away.
我要你立即过来
I'll be right there.
我就来
They've cut me off from my medication.
他们不给我药了
You haven't been cut off.
没有不给
Dr. Hill said you had enough in your system right now.
希尔大夫说再用药就过量了
You need to wait a few hours.
你要过几个小时再服
I don't want to wait a few hours, Mike.
我不想等 麦克
I need something now.
现在就要
What's going on, Mrs. Logan?
到底怎么了 洛根太太?
I don't need counseling, Mike.
我不想被开导 麦克
I just want a damn pill.
我只想要吃药
Sit down. Sit down.
坐下 坐下来
Thank you, agent Adams.
谢谢 亚当斯特工
We've been through some tough times before, Martha.
我们曾渡过难关 玛莎
Just follow the doctor's orders for now.
现在听从医嘱就行
This is more than just a tough time, Mike.
现在不是简单的难关 麦克
None of this is going to go away.
永远都不会渡过
I just have to live with it.
我要一直忍受
What do you mean, "it's not going to go away"?
为什么是 "永远都不会渡过"?
What are you talking about?
你在说什么?
I... I shouldn't have said that.
我不该说的
Martha,
玛莎
it's me.
我靠得住
Say what needs to be said.
有什么尽管说出来
What needs to be said I can't say to you.
我想说但不能说
Why not?
为什么不能?
Listen, Mike,I just...
麦克
I just need to get some sleep.
我想休息休息
I'm just...
我
my nerves are shot from today.
今天我很烦躁
I just need something  to calm me down.
我需要镇静下来
I just need to get to my medication.
我要吃药
The President doesn't want you to leave the room.
总统不愿你离开房间
Then you can bring it here.
那你把药拿来
I just want to take a couple of pills.
我只要吃药
I need to sleep.
休息一会儿
You can watch me take them.
你可以在一边看我吃
I'll see what I can do.
我去试试
yes?
喂?
They found Bauer yet?
找到鲍尔了吗?
No, they haven't.
还没有
That's not good.
这样可不妙
I know that's not good.
我也清楚
I'm putting pressure everywhere I can.
我已到处施加了压力
I don't think I have to tell you how disastrous it would be
如果鲍尔拿到录音带
if Bauer gets his hands on that recording.
你应该清楚后果
That's exactly right.
是的
You don't have to tell me.I know.
不用你提醒 我知道
When I find him,
找到他时
I will call you.
我就通知你
Is there anything else?
有其他事吗?
No.
没了
Good.
好的
Mr. President?
总统先生?
What is it, Mike?
怎么了 麦克?
There's something I think I should call to your attention.
我想告诉你一件事
Yes?
什么?
Your wife is in a very agitated state.
你的夫人情绪很不稳定
I don't know how to proceed.
我不知道该怎么办
Proceed with what?
做什么?
She wants me to bring her her medication against doctor's orders.
她不顾医嘱 让我为她拿药
That's all I need right now is to deal with her!
现在我要的就是敷衍她!
No! No!
不行
No more pills.
不能把药给她
And she shouldn't be wasting your time with this anyway!
她不该浪费你的时间!
Mr. President.
总统先生
Is there something going on that i should know about?
有什么事情是我该知道的吗?
Why?
为什么这么说?
What did she say?
她说了什么?
She needs more medication to calm herself down.
她要用药来镇静
Something's clearly bothering her,
有事情困扰着她
but she didn't want to talk about it.
但她不愿意说
I don't see where any of this becomes your business, Mike.
这和你无关 麦克
I'll tell you where,Mr. President.
有关 总统先生
I'm your chief of staff.
我是你的参谋长
If there's something going on that I don't know about that involves national security,
如果涉及国家安全 而我被蒙在鼓里
it is my business.
那就和我有关
This isn't national security,Mike.
这无关国家安全 麦克
It's our marriage.
是我们的婚姻
I think both of us realized today,
我想我们意识到
At this point,
现在
our relationship is nothing more than a facade,
我们婚姻只是个摆设
and one that we're going to have to keep up for as long as I'm President.
在我还是总统时 会维持下去
I think that she's reacting to that, Mike.
我想她是为了这事 麦克
I see.
知道了
I'm sorry, sir.
抱歉 先生
Mike?
麦克?
Give her what she wants.
把药给她吧
Lord knows, she's in a lot of pain.
不要让她受折磨
Where are you hiding it?
你把东西藏哪了?
Hiding what?
藏什么?
What-what do you want?
你要什么?
What the hell is this?
这是干什么?
I know who you are.
我知道你是谁
I know your connection with omicron.
我知道你和欧米克隆有联系
I know your history with Christopher Henderson.
我知道你认识克里斯托夫・亨德森
He asked you to take something out of the country for him.
他要你帮忙携带东西出国
Where is it?
在哪?
Christopher Henderson?
克里斯托夫・亨德森?
I have not seen him in months.
我几个月没见过他了
Don't you lie to me!
不要对我说谎!
I'm not lying, I swear!
我发誓 没有骗你!
I know Henderson,
我认识亨德森
but I don't know what you're talking about.
但我不知道你说什么
Did you check your luggage?
你检查过你的行李吗?
Yes.
是的
Find it.
找出来
Move!
快!
What are you doing?
你在干什么?
Nothing.
没什么
Homework?
作业?
Homework, yeah.
作业 对
I didn't know they had wifi in here.
我不知道这里可以无线上网
Could you leave me alone?
请走开?
I can't talk right now.
我很忙
You're a little,,
因为现在的宵禁
freaked out because of the curfew thing.
你受到惊吓了
Join the club.
所以来了
Yeah, okay.
是的
When you come up for air,
你有空的话
I'm buying.
可以找我
Airport customs.
机场海关
This is Chloe o' brian from CTU Los Angeles.
我是CTU洛杉矶的科洛伊・奥布赖恩
I need to talk to somebody in passenger clearing.
我需要和机场安检人员通话
I'll need verification.
请确认身份
Agency id: Ctu 99A-12.
编号是 CTU 99A-12
the captain has turned on the fasten seat belt sign,
机长打开了系紧安全带标志
as we are expecting some turbulence.
我们将遭遇气流
Please return to your seat
请坐回座位
and make sure your seat belt is securely fastened.
确认安全带已系紧
the passenger in 12D must be in the forward lavatory.
12D的乘客可能在洗手间
You should get him out.
你要把他领出来
The captain said it's going to shake pretty hard.
机长说之后会很颠簸
There's nobody in those.
没有人在
I just checked.
我检查过了
Then where is this guy?
他去哪了?
I don't know.
不知道
Maybe he changed seats.
也许他换了座位
Call the captain,
告诉机长
and tell him the air marshal's down,
空警被袭
and a passenger's missing!
一位乘客失踪
What's going on here?!
发生什么了?!
Please be seated, sir.
先生 请坐下
Now, sir!
马上 先生
Captain Cotter, this is Dan.
科特机长 我是丹
The air marshal's been assaulted.
空警被袭击
What?
什么?
Assaulted?
袭击?
What's going on back there?
后面怎么了?
I don't know, sir,
不知道
but he's been knocked out,
他被击昏
and a passenger's missing.
而且一位旅客失踪
Okay, okay. Secure the cabin.
好的 保护好机舱
Keep the passengers under control.
稳定好乘客
What's going on?
怎么了?
There's a problem in the cabin.
机舱有问题
Make sure our door is secure.
舱门是否关好
It is.
是的
What kind of problem?
什么问题?
The air marshal's been knocked out.
空警被袭
Call L.A. Center,
通知洛杉矶中心
get vectors for an emergency return.
要求紧急返回
Mr. Avila, what happened?
阿维拉先生 发生什么了?
The man seated next to me
坐在我边上的人
where is he?
他在哪?
I didn't see him.
没看到
We got to find him.
我们要找到他
Damn it.
该死
What?
怎么了?
He's got my gun.
他拿了我的枪
Mike,come in.
麦克 请进
So,do you have something for me?
带来我要的了吗?
This is just enough for a couple of days.
这些够用很多天了
-Dr. Hill's going to come in... -Thank you,Mike.
-希尔医生会  -谢谢 麦克
I'm going to get ready for bed now. Is there something else?
我准备睡觉了 还有其他事吗?
Yes,there is.
当然有
Earlier you said something to the effect
早些时候你说我不知道实情
that I didn't know everything that was going on.
诸如此类的话
I was confused.
我当时糊涂了
I wanted my pills.
我想要我的药
I don't think so.
我不觉得
Are you calling me a liar?
那你准备叫我骗子?
I just spoke with the President.
我刚和总统谈过
And I got the same feeling from him I get from you.
我感到 他和你状况类似
Which is?
那是?
That you're both covering something up.
你们都在隐瞒什么
You know,Mike,I'm the one around here who's supposed to be paranoid,not you.
知道吗 麦克 我才应该是那个多疑的人 而不是你
I know you,Martha.
我了解你 玛莎
And I know the President.
我也了解总统
He said this was all about marital difficulties.
他说都是婚姻的困扰
I think there's something else.
我觉得另有原因
What is it?
是什么?
Don't shut me out.
别隐瞒
Maybe I can help you.
说不定我能帮你
There is something else,Mike,
的确另有原因 麦克
but it's between me and charles.
但是仅限我和查尔斯之间
If that changes,I promise I'll let you know.
如果状况好转了 我承诺我会告诉你的
I don't know what you think Henderson gave me. I saw no one.
我不知道你觉得亨德森会给我什么 我没见任何人
I was picked up at the consulate and brought directly here.
我从使馆出来 就直接来这里了
There are witnesses, you can ask them.
有很多证人 你可以问他们
-Is this your only piece of luggage? -Yes.
-这是你唯一的行李?  -是的
If you're lying to me, I'll find out.
如果你在说谎 我会查明的
I am not lying.Please,
我没说谎 求你了
if there is someone on this plane that has something you want,it is not me.
会不会是飞机上的其他人有你想要的东西 而不是我
Yeah.
喂
Jack,I don't think Hans Meyer is our guy.
杰克 我觉得汉斯・梅尔 不是我们要找的那个
-Why not? -The timeline doesn't match.
-为什么不是?  -时间不符合
He's been in customs for the last three hours clearing himself onto the flight.
最近的3小时 他都一直在海关准备上飞机
-The plane's turning. -What does that mean?
-飞机转向了  -什么意思?
It means they know I'm on board. Chloe,keep looking.
就是说他们知道我登机了 科洛伊 继续查
Okay.
好的
are you sure he's down there?
你确定他就在下面?
There's nowhere else he could be.
他没其他地方可去
Tell the pilot he can do it.
让机长降压吧
But there's a passenger down there with him. He'll die.
但下面还有位乘客 他会死的
There's over 50 passengers up here. Call him now.
上面有超过50位乘客 快打给他
Do it.
快点
Captain,
机长
the air marshal says the baggage area is secure,
空警说行李舱已安全
and that you should begin.
你可以开舱了
air's coming in.
有空气进来了
It's not coming in, it's going out.
不是进来 而是出去了
-What do you mean? -They're depressurizing this area.
-什么意思?  -他们在降压
What's going to happen to us?
对我们有什么影响?
If we don't get into the main cabin, we're going to lose consciousness.
如果我们不回到主舱内 我们就会失去知觉
Jack,what's going on in the plane? Security net just issued a bulletin.
杰克 飞机怎么了? 安全网刚刚发布了一个公告
Chloe,I need you to patch me through to the pilot.
科洛伊 把我暂时接通飞行员
I don't know if I can do that.
我不知道能不能成功
Chloe,they're depressurizing this area. We're going to lose consciousness.
科洛伊 他们在降压 我们会失去知觉
Okay,okay.
好吧
Yeah,Chloe.
恩 科洛伊
Jack needs us to patch him in to the pilot of the flight.
杰克要我们把他连线飞行员
Can you get through on a CTU sub-channel?
你能用CTU的子频道连通吗?
-I'll try. Hold on. -I'll stay on the line.
-我试试 等等  -我在线等
Air control operator 44.
空中管制44号接线员
Yes,I need you to patch me through to the pilot
恩 麻烦以下 请帮我接通
of diplomatic flight five-two-zero out of van nuys.
从范内斯起飞的520号外交飞机
Hey,what do you got? A little voice-over ip going on there?
嘿 你在干嘛? 在打网络电话?
Please leave me alone.
请别妨碍我
No,seriously,I can help.
不 很认真地说 我可以帮忙
I know a way for you to get some free bandwidth.
我知道如何搞到免费带宽
-Really? -Absolutely.
-真的?  -当然了
Sit down.
坐吧
Cool.
好极了
Wow,nice piece.
真不错的机子
Never seen one of these before. What is that?
以前没见过哦 那是什么?
it's a CTU series four.
这是CTU第4代
Chloe,they've opened the line to the pilot. I'll patch him through.
科洛伊 他们接上飞行员了 我给他接通
Thanks.
谢谢
Okay,Jack,I'm putting you on with the pilot.
好了 杰克 准备接飞行员了
Go ahead.
接吧
This is captain stan Cotter. Who am I speaking to?
我是机长斯坦・科特 您哪位?
Captain,my name is Jack Bauer.I'm with the counter terrorist
机长 我叫杰克・鲍尔 洛杉矶CTU也在线
unit in Los Angeles.I'm the man in your baggage hold.
我正在你飞机的行李舱内
What do you think you're doing?
你想干嘛?
I'll explain everything in a moment
我马上解释这一切
but you're going to have to restore air pressure to this area.
但是你先恢复这里的空气压力
Sir,I remind you, I am a federal agent.
先生 我提醒你 我是联邦特工
What kind of a federal agent knocks out an air marshal?I don't believe you.
哪种联邦特工会打昏空警? 我不相信你
Sir,I was patched through to you by a CTU sub-channel.
先生 我通过CTU子频道连上了你
I couldn't have done that unless I had clearance.
除非我被授权 不然我无法连上的
All I know is,you have a gun and you have breached airplane security.
我所知道的是 你有枪 并且你破坏了飞机安全
Captain,this is a matter of national security. Now open the damn hatch!
机长 这和国家安全有关 赶快打开该死的舱门
What do you think?
你认为呢?
He couldn't have patched in through CTU if he was hostile.
如果他是敌方 他不可能通过CTU连接上
There's no point in taking a chance. In a couple of minutes he'll pass out.
我们不需要冒险 几分钟内他就会昏倒
From there, the air marshal can handle it.
那时 空警可以制伏他
Captain,we are running out of air down here.
机长 我们快没空气了
captain,I know you can hear me.
机长 我知道你能听到我
There is a man on board your plane that is a danger to you. That's why I am here.
机上有危险分子 所以我才上了飞机
Open the hatch!
打开舱门!
-I can't do that. -Okay,you son of a bitch.
-我不能那样做  -你等着 杂种
What the hell was that?
怎么回事?
-The aileron conduit's been breached. -What?!
-平衡翼控制器故障  -什么?!
What the hell do you think you're doing? You're going to kill everybody on this plane.
知道你在干嘛吗? 你会害死飞机上的每个人
That's up to you. Open the hatch.
那就看你的了 打开舱门
I'm not letting you up here.
我不会让你上来的
Then you'll be responsible for everything that happens.
那你要为发生的一切负责
All right,all right, all right.
好吧 好吧 好吧
Sue,I'm going to stabilize the pressure and I'm letting him up.I want you to unlock the hatch.
苏 我准备恢复压力让他上来 我要你打开舱门盖
The cockpit's secure. He can't get in here.
驾驶舱安全 他进不来的
Yes,captain.
好的 机长
What do you think you're doing?
你知道你在干嘛吗?
The captain ordered me to open the hatch.
机长命令我打开舱门盖
Both of you,turn around and grab the wall.Now!
你们全都转身 手放墙上 快点!
You... in the baggage hold.
你 去行李舱
Do it. Now.
快点
Close it.
关上它
Lock it.
锁上
-Out of the galley now. -Get back to your seats.
-从厨房出去  -都回座位
-What's going on? -Sit down!
-怎么了?  -坐下!
He has a gun!
他有枪!
everybody just stay in your seats. Face forward.Put your hands on your head.
大家呆在原位 脸朝前 双手放在脑后
Do what I tell you and no one will get hurt. If you don't,people will start to die.
按我说的做 没有人会受伤 如果你们不听 那就会死人
Get the captain on the phone now.
让机长听电话
Sir,he's in the main cabin. He has a gun.
先生 他在主舱内 他有枪
Get the first-class passengers, move them into the main cabin.
让头等舱的乘客到主舱里去
Everyone to the main cabin.
每个人都呆在主舱
Captain,this is Jack Bauer.
机长 我是杰克・鲍尔
I want to assure you I have no intention of hurting any of your passengers.
我想向你保证 我没有伤害任何乘客的意图
I need to find something that's on the plane. It's a matter of national security.
我要找飞机上的某样物品 这有关国家安全
What do you want,Bauer?
你要什么 鲍尔?
I want you to remain in a holding pattern so I can search your passengers.
我要你保持在椭圆形盘旋 以便我搜索你的乘客
If you're really a federal agent, then you know I have to land this plane.
如果你真的是联邦特工 你知道我必须让飞机着陆
Sir,that won't give me enough time.
先生 那就没时间了
That's not my problem.
那不是我的问题
I have a gun.Your air marshal is down. Captain,it is your problem.
我手上有枪 空警在底舱 机长 这是你的问题
You need to remain in a holding pattern, do you understand me?
你要继续飞这条航线 明白吗
You do what you have to do,Mr. Bauer. My job is to land this airplane.
你做你得做的事情 我的任务是让飞机着陆而已
And that is what I am going to do.
而这是我将要做的事
Captain? Captain...
机长 机长
That's all we have on flight 520,sir.
以上为所知520班机的情况
Okay,look,I want updates on the situation on a minute by minute basis if necessary.
如果必要的话我要每分钟更新情报
Yes.sir.
是的长官
Yes.
喂
I just got word from the faa about a hiJacking aboard
我从联邦航空总局得知一个半小时前
a diplomatic flight that left van nuys a half hour ago.
范内斯机场一外交航班被劫持
So what?
然后呢
Jack Bauer is the hiJacker.
杰克是劫机者
What is he doing on that flight?
他在那班航机上干什么
Looking for the recording that implicates me in David Palmer's death.
在上面寻找我和大卫・帕默 死有关的录音带
Henderson handed it off to somebody before he was arrested
亨德森在被拘留前把它交到别人受伤
and Jack must know that it's on board.
杰克一定知道它在机上
Then you shouldn't be wasting your time talking to me.
你还浪费时间和我说这戏废话
Order the plane down, and grab Bauer before he can hurt us.
命令航机着陆 在鲍尔伤害我们前抓住他
Wait,what are you saying? That he hiJacked the plane?
等等 你在说什么 他劫持飞机
Not exactly.He has control of the cabin. The pilot is landing the plane.
他是控制了机舱 驾驶员在降落
What about that recording?
那么那卷录音带呢
He's still looking for it,but there's no guarantee he'll find it before the plane lands.
他仍然在找它 但是不确定他能否在降落前找到
And after that, it's all over.
然后在接下来 就什么都结束了
The President will have his people arrest Jack at the airport and isolate him.
总统会让他的人马 在机场逮捕杰克并隔离他的
What are we supposed to do?
那我们接下来该怎么做
Just keep helping Jack.
继续帮杰克
Chloe,I need to see that evidence. Call me if you need anything from here.
科洛伊 我要看那个证据 如果需要任何帮忙打电话给我
Fine.
好的
Give me a second.
给我点时间
What's Bauer doing on flight 520?
鲍尔在520班机上做什么?
You have no idea what you're dealing with, you little ass-kisser.
你不知道你现在做什么 马屁精
You don't talk to my people like that,Bill.
比尔你不需要跟我的人这样说话
Take him to holding.
带他到拘留室
It's no wonder CTU fell apart under that guy.
毫无疑问在这个人管理下CTU已经分裂
Miles,I know you're trying to help, but I'll take it from here,okay?
迈尔斯 我知道你要帮忙 但现在我来接手
Western operations.
西部指挥所
This is Miles papazian, homeland security,Los Angeles.
我是迈尔斯・帕帕赞恩 洛杉矶国土安全部
Pass code 21 double six.
认证码是2166
-Put me through to Mike Novick. -One moment,please.
-帮我接通麦克・诺维克  -请稍等
Yes,Miles. What is it?
喂 迈尔斯 什么事啊
I need your input,sir,because
我需要你的支持 长官 因为
I'm having a problem with Karen Hayes.
我和凯伦・海因斯之间有矛盾
I'd like to preface what I'm about to tell you by saying
首先声明我将要告诉您的事情
that I don't wish to be second-guessing...
都是经过反复和仔细思考的
I don't have time for prefaces.
我没时间听开场白
Karen Hayes was called in to replace Bill Buchanan.
凯伦・海因斯被委任取代比尔・布坎南
She was hand-chosen by the vice President to take that post.
她是副总统亲自挑选才获任
I understand that,sir.
我明白这个
Are you saying you feel she's unfit to do the job?
你是不是说你觉得她不能胜任这工作
Four hours ago,she relieved Bill Buchanan for ineffectual leadership.
四小时前 她免除比尔・布坎南的领导权
He's been working covertly with Chloe O'brian
后者掩护科洛伊・奥布赖恩
to aid Jack Bauer,a federal fugitive.
去帮助联邦通缉犯杰克・鲍尔
Which means Buchanan needs to be dealt with appropriately.
意味着需要小心处理布坎南
What has Karen done?
凯伦做了什么
She sent in a tac team to pick them both up,
她派了一支队伍去抓他们 但是他们到达时
but by the time they got there,O'brian was gone.
奥布赖恩已经不在了
But instead of having the team do the interrogation of Buchanan onsite,
抓到后不去审问布坎南
Karen wasted 20 minutes by bringing him in to CTU.
凯伦用了20分钟带他回CTU
Maybe she felt the interrogation would be more effective with CTU resources.
也许她觉得用CTU的资源更有助审问
But,sir,she isn't even using rudimentary CTU resources.
但是 长官 她甚至不用CTU的基本资料
She wants to do a soft Q and A by herself.
她用自己柔和的方式去问问题
Any leads we may have had on O'brian have dried up.
这样我们也许就 不能从奥布赖恩那得到什么
Wait a second,Miles.
等等迈尔斯
I'm not going to pass judgment on Karen Hayes at this point.
我不会凭这点去评价凯伦・海因斯
She's not interrogating a terrorist.
她不是在对一个恐怖分子进行审问
She's dealing with a high-ranking federal employee.
她是在处理一个高级联邦官员
Sometimes finesse and diplomacy are better than coercion.
有时候政策和手段技巧 比高压更为有效
Your concern is duly noted,Miles.
你的关心是很正常的迈尔斯
If you'll excuse me, I need to see the President.
我必须走了 去找一下总统先生
-Karen. -Shut up,Bill.
-凯伦  -比尔 给我闭嘴
We're offline. Now we can talk.
我们离线了 现在我们可以谈谈了
Look,you can continue this charade of me being under arrest
你可以继续在我被捕后这样伪装
if you want to,but Jack needs our help.
但是杰克需要我们帮忙
And he's getting it, but make no mistake,
而且他快要拿到证据 别弄错了
I am still in charge of this facility,
我仍然是这里的主管
and until I see that evidence,I must remain skeptical.
除非我看到证据 不然会保持怀疑
-Have you talked to Chloe? -Yes.
-你和科洛伊说过了吗?  -对
What's Jack's status?
杰克现在怎么样
He's searching the cabin for the evidence, but the pilot is going to land that plane.
在他机舱找证据 但是驾驶员准备降落
-How much time does Jack have? -15 minutes.
-杰克还有多长时间  -15分钟
To search over 50 passengers? That's impossible.
搜查超过50位乘客 这根本不可能
Ms. Hayes.
喂
The President and Mike Novick want an update
总统先生和麦克・诺维克
on the hiJacking of the diplomatic flight.
想要劫持外交航机的最新情况
Put them through.
接他们进来
Go ahead,sir.
请讲 先生
Ms. Hayes,this is the President. Talk to me about 520.
海因斯女士 我是总统 跟我说有关520航机的事
We know that Bauer's involved,but we don't know why.
我们知道鲍尔和这事有关 但是我们不知道原因
Isn't it obvious?Bauer is a fugitive and
这还不清楚吗 鲍尔是个通缉犯
he's looking for safe passage out of the country.
他在找一个安全离境的方法
Well,that's certainly a possibility,sir.
是的 这是一个可能性的 总统先生
Listen to me. This man is desperate. He will say or do anything.
听我说 他没退路了 任何事都干得出来
He's not to be trusted.
他不值得再信任
We need to take him down now, dead or alive.
无论死活 都要拿下他
Yes,sir.
是的 总统先生
-Mr. President. -Look.
-总统先生  -听着
You call the pilot and you tell him that
你可以告诉驾驶员
I don't care if Bauer is making threats or not,
我不管鲍尔是不是在恐吓
that plane has to land immediately.
飞机必须马上着陆
And when it lands,I want my
一旦飞机落地
secret service detail to take him into custody,is that clear?
我要特勤处马上将鲍尔拘押
Ms. Hayes?
海因斯女士?
Yes,Mr. President.
是的 总统先生
The President has had knowledge of everything that's happened today.
总统早知道今天发生的事情了
He wants that plane down before Jack finds the evidence.
他想在杰克找到证据以前就让飞机降落
We have to buy him more time.
我们必须拖延时间
I don't have the authority to keep that plane from landing.
我无权阻止飞机降落
Sir.
先生
-It still doesn't make sense to me. -What?
-事情说不通  -什么?
Jack Bauer has been on the right side
今天开始 直到现在
of everything that's happened today,up until now.
杰克・鲍尔的立场都是对的
Well,right now,he is hiJacking a plane. This man is not stupid.
可现在他劫持了飞机 他不是傻子
He's appeared to do the right thing,but right now,
他表面做正确的事
he's backed into a corner,and he's desperate.
背地里作困兽斗
-Do you really believe that,sir? -I absolutely do.
-你真的相信?  -绝对信
Bauer's lied to us all day.
鲍尔一直在欺骗我们
He's played us all for fools.
他耍了所有人
-Flight operations. -This is Chloe O'brian again.
-班机调度  -还是我 科洛伊・奥布赖恩
Yes,ms. O'brian.
是的 奥布赖恩女士
The copilot,Don Faganson,didn't check in when he boarded flight 520.
副驾驶邓・费甘森 在登机前没有登记
Mr. Faganson didn't board.
费甘森先生没有登机
-Why not? -He was replaced at the last minute.
-为什么?  -他在最后被替换了
-By whom? -Scott Evans,the new copilot.
-被谁?  -斯科特・埃文斯 新的副驾驶
Here are your things, go back to your seat.
还给你 请回座位
-yeah. -Jack,it's the copilot,scott Evans.
-什么  -杰克 是副驾驶 斯科特・埃文斯
-How do you know? -He used to fly for hatton air.
-你怎么知道的?  -他曾为哈德顿航空工作
It's a private charter company that worked exclusively for omicron.
是家只为欧米克隆服务的包机公司
Evans was assigned to Henderson's group.
埃文斯分配给亨德森的部门
He flew him around for over a year.
为他工作了一年多
Okay,I need you to patch me through to the captain
我要你接通我和机长私聊的频道
on a discreet channel so Evans can't hear me.
以防埃文斯可能听见对话内容
Okay.
好的
Sit down! Now!
坐下! 马上!
Everybody stay in your seats and no one  will get hurt!
想活命的话 就都坐下!
-You okay? -I'm fine.
-你没事吧?  -很好
Incoming com on line 139.
139线上的通话
Go ahead.
说吧
Captain,this is Jack Bauer. I'm speaking to you on a discreet channel.
机长 我是杰克・鲍尔 我们之间的通话是私密的
The person that I'm looking for,
我要找的人
the man with the evidence that I need,is sitting next to you.
持有我需要的证据的人就坐在你边上
He's your copilot, scott Evans.
你的副驾驶 斯科特・埃文斯
That's ridiculous.
荒谬
Sir,my sources have informed me that Evans was a last-second replacement.
我得到消息 埃文斯是最后一刻才被替换的
Can you explain to me why you're not flying with your regular copilot,Don Faganson?
你能解释下为什么 以前的副驾驶邓・费甘森不在吗?
Captain,scott Evans has been connected to a known terrorist.
斯科特・埃文斯与恐怖分子是一伙的
You need to open the door.
你一定要开门
This conversation is over.
通话结束了
Damn it.
该死
What did he want?
他要干什么?
He's desperate. Wants us to land.
他要我们降落
-This is messed up. -Yeah.
-真是一团糟  -是啊
Bad luck for you,huh?
你不走运?
Why?
为什么?
Well,wasn't don supposed to have your seat tonight?
本来是邓出勤的?
Yeah.
对
What happened to him?
他怎么了?
I don't know. I got the call,so I'm here.
不清楚 我得到通知 就来了
Yeah.
哦
Oh,god.
天哪
What's wrong?
怎么了?
could you,uh...could you take the stick for a second?
能帮我握一下操纵杆吗?
You okay?
你还好吧?
Yeah. I just... got a cramp in my leg.
脚抽筋了
Yeah. Those are a bitch.
是啊 真够烦人的
Yeah.
是啊
I'm the only one who can fly this plane.
只有我能驾驶了
Now,you don't strike me as a man who's willing to die for Christopher Henderson.
别告诉我你为了 克里斯托夫・亨德森愿意吃子弹
Give me the recording.
把录音交出来
Do it.
快
Slowly. Get up.
慢慢站起来
Get back in your seat.
回座位去
You're going to land this plane or I'm going to put a bullet in your head.
要么降落 要么脑袋给你打个洞
Yeah,Jack.
喂 杰克
Advise CTU I have the recording.
通知CTU我拿到了录音
I'll be on the ground in less than 15 minutes.
15分钟内就能降落
Got it.
了解
-Yes. -Charles.
-喂  -查尔斯
If I'm going to live with this, then you're going to have to help me.
如果想让我忍下去 你就要帮我
Help you do what,Martha?
怎么帮你 玛莎?
Understand.
理解
I...
我
I know you're a good man,
我知道你是好人
and that deep down,
你本意
you do what's best for this country.
是为了这个国家
Of course I do.
当然
Then why...
为什么
why didn't you come to me?
你不和我说呢?
I'd have been there for you.
我会帮助你
I could have talked you through it.
为你开导的
For god's sake,Martha,for the last three years,
看在上帝的份上 玛莎过去3年中
you've been one click away from a nervous breakdown every single day,
你的精神状况一直处于濒临崩溃状态
and I'm gonna come to you for advice?
你让我怎么敢向你咨询
-I'm gonna have to take another call. -No. Charles,no,no.
-我还要接电话  -不要挂 查尔斯 不要
We'll talk later.
再谈
Yes.
喂
Bauer's got the evidence. He is in control of the plane.
鲍尔得到了证据 控制了飞机
How do you know that?
你怎么会知道?
We just picked up a call from Chloe O'brian to Karen Hayes.
我们截取了 科洛伊・奥布赖恩和凯伦・海因斯的通话
What do we do?
我们该怎么办?
You are going to have to shoot down that plane,Mr. President.
你得击落飞机 总统先生
-What? -It's the only option we've got.
-什么?  -只有这个选择
Otherwise,you go to prison for treason and murder.
不然 你会因为叛国和谋杀而入狱